jackpot.com 2007-03-12

# Quick! Search --> <%%search:query/%%>

| 

**ATTENTION JACKPOT.COM USERS:  
** As of 11:59pm Eastern Time on September 30, 2006, jackpot.com will no longer be an active web site and participation in the jackpot.com games will no longer be available. All LuckyLoot must be used before 11:59pm Eastern Time on September 20, 2006. After that date, all unused LuckyLoot will become invalid and may not be redeemed for entries into sweepstakes. We thank you for your participation in and support of jackpot.com.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

The following applies only to California residents.

Jackpot.com may, from time to time, share your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As a California resident, you have a legal right to request and receive in writing or by email the names and addresses of all such third parties who received your personally identifiable information during the previous calendar year and a list of the types of personally identifiable information disclosed to such third parties. To request such information, send an email to [yourprivacy@jackpot.com](mailto:yourprivacy@jackpot.com) or write to California Privacy Information c/o Jackpot.com, 2101 Rosecrans, Suite 2000, El Segundo, CA 90245 or fax to (888)269-3836. We will not honor such request more than once per calendar year.

For more information on how your personally identifiable information is collected and used, please read our Privacy Policy.

|  | **Rules/Policies: Privacy Policy**  
---|---  
  
Effective as of January 1, 2005 

Jackpot.com ("Jackpot.com") makes this Web site (the "Site") available to registered members of the Site ("Members"), subject to this privacy policy (the "Policy") and the Jackpot.com User Agreement ("Member Agreement"). This Policy explains what information Jackpot.com collects about Members on the Site, how Jackpot.com uses this information, and how such information is maintained. By registering and using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, in whole or part, you should not use this Site, or if you are a Member, you must immediately terminate your account.

Note that this Policy applies only with respect to the information collected on the Site and not any information collected or obtained through other methods or sources.

| **Personally Identifiable Information**  
---|---  
  
**Collection of PII**  
Jackpot.com only collects Member personally identifiable information ("PII") that is volunteered by Members during the registration process or in response to specific information requests explicitly presented to Members. To register to become a Member, you will be requested to provide the following PII: first and last name, address, email address, telephone number, gender and date of birth. . You will also be asked to provide a password, which you will need to access various features offered on the site. In addition, during registration or at another time, you might be asked to provide other demographic and/or financial information and/or information concerning your physical characteristics. In order to allow Jackpot.com to comply with applicable legal reporting requirements, Members who win certain prizes on the Site may be requested to provide their social security number. However, Jackpot.com will otherwise never share this social security information other than as required by law for tax and reporting purposes. From time to time, Jackpot.com may also present opportunities for Members to voluntarily provide a limited amount of general demographic information about themselves, which may include their gender, birth date, marital status, education, occupation, and household income. 

**Use and Sharing of PII**  
Jackpot.com reserves the right to use Member PII: (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided; (2) as disclosed at the time such information is provided; and (3) as disclosed in this Policy. However, Members should note that Jackpot.com may change this Policy at any time (See "Changes to this Policy," below), and that therefore Jackpot.com may in the future use Member PII for additional purposes not currently included in this Policy.

When you register to become a Member of this Site, you are automatically registered to become a Member of all the other online properties in the Vendare Network (collectively, the "Network Sites") Accordingly, Jackpot.com may share Member PII with the Network Sites. For a list of the Network Sites, please see your Jackpot.com member profile, which you can view by clicking here.

Also, Jackpot.com may share Member PII (except for credit card information and social security number) with its partners, sponsors, advertisers, service providers and marketers lookup and reference services and any other entities that Jackpot.com believes are able to provide Members with special offers and opportunities. Note that although Jackpot.com advises everyone who receives Member PII from Jackpot.com to support this Policy, Jackpot.com has no control over such party's information handling practices and is not responsible for any failure of such party to adhere to this Policy.

As provided in the Member Agreement, Members are required to provide their PII to Jackpot.com as a condition of Membership, and to understand and agree that Jackpot.com may share their PII with the Network Sites and unaffiliated third parties as provided in this Policy. If you do not provide the required PII or do not agree that Jackpot.com may share your PII with such entities as set forth in this Policy, you may not register as a Member, and if you are already a Member, you must immediately terminate your account, by following the instructions in the "Terminate Account" section below.

Additionally, Jackpot.com may share Member PII in aggregate, non-personal form, with select companies that wish to reach a particular Member target audience (e.g., registered female Members between the ages of 25-35, who have an average household income of over $50,000.00). This information will allow these entities to provide relevant offers to specific Members.

Finally, Jackpot.com may disclose Member PII in order to: (1) comply with applicable laws; (2) respond to governmental inquiries; (3) comply with valid legal process; and (4) protect the rights or property of Jackpot.com, the Network Sites or other Members of this Site.

By registering and using this Site, Members acknowledge that the processing of their PII for the purposes described above may involve the transfer of such PII from within the European Economic Area ("EEA") to countries outside the EEA whose data protection regulation may not be as stringent as that within the European Union.

| **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
---|---  
  
Jackpot.com also collects certain non-personally identifiable information as more fully described below. 

_Cookies._ Jackpot.com uses "cookies" on the Site. Cookies are small pieces of information that Jackpot.com's server places on an individual's computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with the Site. For example, Jackpot.com will place a cookie on a Member's computer when he/she initially registers with the Site. The next time that Member visits the Site, Jackpot.com's server will recognize the cookie (and the Member) and the Member may begin playing games on the Site without the need to sign in.

While some Web browsers allow a Member to automatically reject all cookies or be notified when a cookie is about to be placed on the Member's computer, disabling this feature may compromise the efficiency and added services that cookies provide. It is not Jackpot.com's intention to use cookies to retrieve information that is unrelated to this Site or your interaction with this Site.

_IP Address._ Jackpot.com collects your IP (Internet Protocol) address to help diagnose problems with Jackpot.com's server, and to administer this Site. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. Your IP address is also used to help identify you during a particular session and to gather broad demographic data.

_Clear GIFs._ Jackpot.com uses a common technology known as a "Clear GIF" or "1-by-1 Pixel" on the Site and in e-mail communications with Members. A Clear GIF, or "graphic interface format" is a small graphic (in fact, truly a 1x1 pixel) that Jackpot.com (or a partner of Jackpot.com) places on a page of the Site. Jackpot.com may also occasionally place GIFs in e-mail messages that it sends to Members. GIFs, which do not contain any PII, provide Jackpot.com with important information about how Members use the Site and respond to e-mail messages. With this information, Jackpot.com is better able to track the performance of certain promotions and understand the effectiveness of particular creative e-mail presentations. Jackpot.com may also allow its advertisers and promotional partners the ability to use GIFs on the Site solely to track Members who link from their respective sites to this Site, but this ability to track such activity does not allow these entities access to Member PII.

Although the information collected through the foregoing methods does not itself contain any PII, Jackpot.com may analyze and match such information with other information that you provide on this Site (including PII) as well as information that Jackpot.com may obtain elsewhere, and Jackpot.com may share all or some of such information with partners, prospective partners, and other affiliated or unaffiliated third parties.

Jackpot.com may also disclose any of the non-personally identifiable information described above in order to (1) comply with applicable laws (including, without limitation, the CAN-SPAM Act), (2) respond to governmental inquiries, (3) comply with valid legal process, or (4) protect the rights or property of Jackpot.com, the Network Sites or Members of this Site.

| **Agents**  
---|---  
  
Jackpot.com may employ other companies and individuals to perform services on its behalf and on behalf of the Network Sites, such as (1) administering sweepstakes, contests and other promotions, (2) sending emails, (3) providing marketing assistance, and (4) database management and analysis. Such companies and individuals will have access to Member PII only to the extent necessary to perform their services, but will not be permitted to use it for any other purpose. 

| **Linking of Information**  
---|---  
  
Jackpot.com may combine information provided by a Member with information obtained from other sources. Enhancing Member files with this other information will allow Jackpot.com to provide Members with more relevant services and promotional offers. For example, a Member's user profile will automatically be updated with any information that user enters on any of the Network Sites. Likewise, any information entered on this Site will be used to update the Member's profile on all of the Network Sites. 

| **Opt-Out of Jackpot.com Email Promotions**  
---|---  
  
When you register to become a Member of the Site, you will automatically be registered to receive promotional offers and site updates, via emails, from Jackpot.com and from the Network Sites and other associated email brands. 

Additionally, when you register to become a Member on the Site, you will be provided with the opportunity to receive promotional offers, via emails, from partners of Jackpot.com. While some of these opportunities will only be sent to you if you expressly request them, others may be sent to you unless you elect not to receive them. Accordingly, when you register, please review these offers carefully.

Members may, at any time, choose not to receive promotional emails from Jackpot.com, the Network Sites or partners of Jackpot.com by (1) following the "unsubscribe" instructions in the Jackpot.com e-mail, or (2) terminating their Jackpot.com account. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Jackpot.com may continue to contact Members for the purpose of communicating information about their membership with Jackpot.com, changes in features of the Site, or similar information relating to Jackpot.com, the Site or your membership, as well as to facilitate, complete or confirm any transaction that Members' enter into or in response to or fulfillment of Members' inquiries or requests.

_Note that unsubscribing from one email list does not automatically unsubscribe you from any other email list that you may be on. Please read the email carefully to find out which list you are unsubscribing from. If you would like to unsubscribe from all email lists, you must terminate your account._

| **Access to Information**  
---|---  
  
If you want to review, correct or change your profile details (such as your address, email address or telephone numbers), please go to the Help section of the Site, and follow the appropriate instructions. 

| **Third Party Services**  
---|---  
  
Certain activities and services available on the Site are provided by entities not affiliated with Jackpot.com. For example, if you choose to purchase a product or service from the Site or play a game presented by a partner of Jackpot.com, the information you provide on the Site in connection with such purchase or game may be made available to that other party to satisfy that purpose. Although Jackpot.com advises all of its partners to support this Policy, Jackpot.com has no control over their information handling practices and is not responsible for any failure of such partners to adhere to this Policy. 

| **Third Party Cookies**  
---|---  
  
In the course of serving advertisements to this Site, third-party advertisers or ad servers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The use of cookies by such third party advertisers or ad servers are not subject to this Policy, but are subject to their own respective privacy policies. 

| **Links from the Site**  
---|---  
  
This Site provides links to many of Jackpot.com's advertiser and partner Web sites. If you link to any of these third party Web sites, this Policy will not apply to your use of, and activities on, those sites. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on these sites, including their privacy policies. Jackpot.com shall have no responsibility or liability for your visitation to, and the data collection and use practices of, these sites. 

| **Note Concerning Visitors Under 18 Years of Age**  
---|---  
  
Unless otherwise noted on the Site, the Site and the games available on the Site, are neither intended for, nor directed to, children under the age of 18. Except as otherwise noted on the Site, if Jackpot.com learns that a person who registers on the Site is under the age of 18, Jackpot.com will promptly terminate that individual's account. 

| **Security**  
---|---  
  
While Jackpot.com takes reasonable precautions to safeguard information transmitted between the Site and Members, Jackpot.com is unable to prevent unauthorized access to such information by third parties. Members acknowledge this risk when communicating with the Site. 

| **Consent to Processing**  
---|---  
  
By providing PII and other information to this Site, Members fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in, and the transfer of such information to, the United States and other countries or territories, in accordance with the terms of this Policy. 

| **Transfer in Certain Circumstances**  
---|---  
  
In its sole discretion, Jackpot.com may transfer, sell or assign information collected on and through this Site, including without limitation, PII and other Member-provided information, to one or more third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of Jackpot.com. 

| **Change Account Options and Terminating Account**  
---|---  
  
If you wish to update your email subscription or change any of your profile details (such as your address, email address or telephone number) you must navigate to your profile page that you can access through the help section of the Site. Members of the Site who disagree with any provision of this Policy must immediately terminate their account with Jackpot.com. Accounts may be terminated by visiting the Help section of the Site and following the applicable instructions, or by emailing Jackpot.com customer service at [customerservice@jackpot.com](mailto:customerservice@jackpot.com). All inquiries concerning the use of Member PII by a third party who has received such Member PII as provided in this Policy must be communicated to that third party, and not to Jackpot.com. 

| **Changes to this Policy**  
---|---  
  
Jackpot.com may, from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or part, in its sole discretion. Depending on the nature of the change, Jackpot.com will either announce the change (1) on the home page of the Site, or (2) provide such notice via e-mail to Members. By continuing to use the Site following an announcement of any changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or part, you must terminate your account by visiting the Help section of the Site and following the appropriate instructions. 

Presented by:  
Jackpot.com  
2101 Rosecrans, Suite 2000  
El Segundo, CA 90245
